http://www.cmap.illinois.gov/about/terms-and-conditions

Privacy Statement
The Chicago Metropolitan Agency for Planning (CMAP) online privacy statement applies to information collected through this website and e-mail lists. For questions about this policy, please contact us at 312-454-0400 or info@cmap.illinois.gov.
CMAP does not share or disclose any personal information, including your name, address, or e-mail address with other organizations. Only the CMAP staff and our authorized agents (who agree to our privacy policy) have access to personally identifiable information provided by visitors to our site.
CMAP analyzes its website logs to constantly improve the value of its Web site. The agency uses an external service to provide real-time reporting of browser accesses to our site. This includes page views, unique views, unique visitors, repeat visitors, frequency of visits, and peak-volume traffic periods. We do not use this service to gather, request, record, require, collect, or track any internet users' personally identifiable information.
CMAP maintains several e-mail lists to keep our partners and other interested parties informed of our activities. Individuals must affirmatively request to join our mailing lists, and they may 'opt out' of the list at any time. Additionally, we do not share the e-mail addresses on our lists with outside businesses or organizations. Only the CMAP staff and our authorized agents have access to personally identifiable information provided by visitors to our site.
This privacy policy is subject to occasional revision, and any substantial changes in the way personal Information is used will be posted on the website. Any visitor who objects to any such changes must cease using the website. Continued use of the website following notice of any such changes shall indicate acknowledgement of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes.
Terms and Conditions
Those who choose to comment on the website may select whether or not to have their comments published on the site and in publications at the time of submission. Comments submitted without publication approval will be reviewed by CMAP internally only and not made public. Comments are also moderated to prevent spam and abuse.
CMAP does not endorse and is not responsible for the accuracy or reliability of statements made by third parties on our website.
Materials published on this website are ©Chicago Metropolitan Agency for Planning unless otherwise noted.
To Top
Oct 24, 2013
Terms and Conditions
Jump to section
Privacy Statement
Terms and Conditions
Privacy Statement
The Chicago Metropolitan Agency for Planning (CMAP) online privacy statement applies to information collected through this website and e-mail lists. For questions about this policy, please contact us at 312-454-0400 or info@cmap.illinois.gov.
CMAP does not share or disclose any personal information, including your name, address, or e-mail address with other organizations. Only the CMAP staff and our authorized agents (who agree to our privacy policy) have access to personally identifiable information provided by visitors to our site.
CMAP analyzes its website logs to constantly improve the value of its Web site. The agency uses an external service to provide real-time reporting of browser accesses to our site. This includes page views, unique views, unique visitors, repeat visitors, frequency of visits, and peak-volume traffic periods. We do not use this service to gather, request, record, require, collect, or track any internet users' personally identifiable information.
CMAP maintains several e-mail lists to keep our partners and other interested parties informed of our activities. Individuals must affirmatively request to join our mailing lists, and they may 'opt out' of the list at any time. Additionally, we do not share the e-mail addresses on our lists with outside businesses or organizations. Only the CMAP staff and our authorized agents have access to personally identifiable information provided by visitors to our site.
This privacy policy is subject to occasional revision, and any substantial changes in the way personal Information is used will be posted on the website. Any visitor who objects to any such changes must cease using the website. Continued use of the website following notice of any such changes shall indicate acknowledgement of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes.
Terms and Conditions
Those who choose to comment on the website may select whether or not to have their comments published on the site and in publications at the time of submission. Comments submitted without publication approval will be reviewed by CMAP internally only and not made public. Comments are also moderated to prevent spam and abuse.
CMAP does not endorse and is not responsible for the accuracy or reliability of statements made by third parties on our website.
Materials published on this website are ©Chicago Metropolitan Agency for Planning unless otherwise noted.
To Top
